{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Name the TV shows that featured these memorable characters. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Friends",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Phoebe Buffay"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sesame Street",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Big Bird"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Simpsons",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Milhouse"
  }, {
    "answer": "Seinfeld",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Kramer"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sex and the City",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Carrie Bradshaw"
  }, {
    "answer": "Happy Days",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "The Fonz"
  }, {
    "answer": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Barney Stinson"
  }, {
    "answer": "24",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Jack Bauer"
  }, {
    "answer": "Family Guy",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Quagmire"
  }, {
    "answer": "Full House",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Uncle Jesse"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Cosby Show",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Clair Huxtable"
  }, {
    "answer": "The X-Files",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Fox Mulder"
  }, {
    "answer": "Frasier",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Niles Crane"
  }, {
    "answer": "Married... with Children",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Al Bundy"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Office",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Dwight Schrute"
  }, {
    "answer": "Family Matters",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Urkel"
  }, {
    "answer": "CSI: Miami",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Horatio Caine"
  }, {
    "answer": "Family Ties",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Alex P. Keaton"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lost",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "John Locke"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hawaii Five-O",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Danny \"Danno\" Williams"
  }, {
    "answer": "Beverly Hills, 90210",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Brenda Walsh"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Dukes of Hazzard",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Uncle Jesse"
  }, {
    "answer": "Twin Peaks",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Agent Dale Cooper"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Wire",
    "category": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
    "question": "Stringer Bell"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Memorable American TV Characters Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/memorable-tv-characters-quiz.php"
}